fitnessroar.com 2018-07-10

# Privacy Policy - Fitness Roar

## Privacy Policy

Thank you for your interest in FitnessRoar services and privacy info. Please note that our privacy policy doesn’t apply to that information which you already have posted publicly or display on this site. In general submission of your personal information is not at all required in order to browse FitnessRoar, you can surf this site without revealing any of your personal information.

**Information we collect:**

Without revealing any personal information, one can visit FitnessRoar any time. But, in case, if you register with the FitnessRoar and take part in its various activities like posting a comment, enrolling in a contest then you may be asked to provide your personally identifiable information such as your name, email address, address, contact no. etc along with some non-personally identifiable information like your location, personal & professional interests, age, gender, your experience with FitnessRoar and its services etc. Also, we may get data about our users from the third parties.

Further, in case, you are connecting with FitnessRoar via any social networking site like Facebook, twitter, etc then we are free to collect your profile information from that particular site and not liable for the same.

**Note:**  We respect our visitors/users rights and support “Right to be forgotten”. If you think you’ve ever shared your contact details with us & want us to remove that info, please contact us at  [info@fitnessroar.com](mailto:info@fitnessroar.com)

**Sharing and use of personal information-**

Although we use industry’s best standard measures to protect your personal information in our database we cannot have control over the other users with whom you share your user profile and information.  
We may use the user information:-  
• In order to improve our website  
• To improve our content and products information  
• To rectify the correct info or content given on the site, if any  
• To make our beloved readers participate in various contests, surveys etc.

However, we do not disclose your personal information to others without your approval or in the occurrence of some

**Specific Incidents:-**

• In order to take any action against suspected illegal activities/ violation against our terms and provisions  
• To enforce or imply terms and conditions and privacy policies  
• To protect our reputation, property and our rights/ rights of third party and personal safety of the users  
• We may also disclose personal information if it is required by the law to do so in a good belief because it is necessary to disclose such info to counter court orders or miscellaneous legal processes.  
• In the case of transferring or selling the website to other company so user’s info will be transferred to. We may disclose non-identifiable data to third parties which don’t include your name, email address or contact number.

**What about ‘Cookies’?**

‘Cookies’ are small pieces of information of any website you are visiting which may be stored on your computer’s hard drive. Thus, it may also possible that reader will be served cookies by us, by our advertisers or by that company which help us delivering advertising on this site. These cookies help us and advertisers to identify users on our site and on other sites as well.

**Third Party links:**

This site may contain links, photos etc of third party websites. If you wish to visit another website, we are not at all responsible for the content, image, privacy and terms of use of those websites. It is solely your responsibility to carefully read and review the websites to confirm that understand and abide by their policies.

**Policy updation**

We may change or update our Policy from time to time. In the case of making any material change in which user’s info will be treated then we will inform you of such changes by updating any tagline like ‘updated privacy policy’ etc. Any updated privacy policy will come into immediate effect as soon as it is posted on this site.

**Google Analytics**

We use Google Analytics to track visitors on this site. Google Analytics uses cookies to collect this data.In order to be compliant with the new regulation Google included a data processing amendment.The data we collect will be processed anonymously and “Data sharing” is disabled.We don’t use other Google services in combination with Google Analytics cookies.

**Contact Us**

For getting any further information about FitnessRoar, please email us at-  [info@fitnessroar.com](mailto:info@fitnessroar.com)
